有一个叫做词法作用域的东西。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: JavaScript has
this thing called lexical scope.
词法范围只是意味着,
Lexical scope just means,
当你调用一个函数的时候，它的值是多少，对吗？
what is the value of this when
you invoke a function, right?
这很重要，如果你处理,
This is important if you deal with,
构建一个单页的应用程序，你有一些组件
building something like a single-page app,
and you have components, and
这些组件具有与 DOM 事件绑定的内容。
those components have things
that are bound to DOM events.
你需要确保你的事件以一种允许你的方式发生
You need to make sure that your events
fire in a way that allows you to
在你的组件上访问东西，让事情变得美好和方便。
access stuff on your component,
to make things nice and convenient.
这实际上是一个函数签名的一部分
So this is actually part
of a function signature, so
如果你在定义一个函数？
if you're defining a function?
通常，它是一个在类上下文之外的函数,
And usually, it's gonna be a function
that's outside the context of a class,
对，因为班级已经帮我们搞定了。
right, cuz classes already
kinda handle this for us.
但是如果你真的要依靠能力去做一些事情
But if you're gonna really depend
on being able to do something
就像我们现在所做的，我们需要它的价值是正确的。
like what we're doing here,
we need the value of this to be correct.
所以你只需要在一开始输入你的函数签名,
So you only need to put in your function
signature at the very beginning,
在一个叫做这个的伪参数下
under a pseudo-parameter called this, and
会进行类型检查，确保一切正常。
type-checking will be done to make
sure that everything looks okay.
我要创建一个满足这个约束的对象
So I'm gonna create an object that
kind of meets this constraint, so
我们可以看到，探索这是如何工作的。
that we can see, explore how this works.
有一个电子邮件和一个电话号码，我们走，在这里。
Has both an email and a phone number,
there we go, down here.
我创建了一个函数叫做 invokeSoon,
And I'm creating a function
called invokeSoon,
它故意将 null 作为词法范围传递。
and it's deliberately passing
null along as the lexical scope.
这有点做作，但是
And it's a little bit contrived, but
我只是想告诉你这是怎么回事。
I'm just trying to show
you kinda how this works.
迈克 · 诺斯: 所以如果我们试图引用这个,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
If we try to invoke this,
我们会发现仅仅传递邮件是不够的，对吗？
we'll see that it's not enough
to just pass email along, right?
我们这里有一个字符串，可以是电子邮件或电话。
We have a string here that can be email or
phone.
不管我选择哪一个，我仍然得到一个类型检查错误，和
No matter which one I pick,
I still get a type-checking error, and
原因是，这个约束没有得到满足。
the reason is,
this constraint is not satisfied.
我们可以用两种方法来解决,
We could solve this two ways,
我们可以绑定函数 Mike North: 创建一个绑定版本的
we could bind the function,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Create a bound version of
函数。
the function.
所以在幕后我们围绕函数创建了一个闭包,
So behind the scenes, we're creating
a closure around the function,
并确保使用正确的词法范围调用它。
and ensuring that it's invoked
with the correct lexical scope.
或者我们可以使用 call 和 apply，以及
Or we could use call and apply, and
在最近的一次打字稿发布会上，我不知道是哪一个,
as of a very recent TypeScript release,
it escapes me which one,
您可以使用 bind、 call 和 apply 启用严格的类型检查。
you can enable strict type-checking
with bind, call, and apply.
你不常遇到这种情况但现在你什么都明白了,
You don't run into this a lot, but
now you understand everything,
所有你真正需要知道的，开始函数。
everything you really need to know
to get started with functions.
请注意，当然，我们不，这似乎是一个额外的论点,
And note that, of course, we don't,
this appears to be an additional argument,
你不必向这个函数传递两个参数。
you do not have to pass two
arguments to this function.
这个函数仍然接受一个参数。
This function accepts one parameter,
still.